Guide to the David Starr Jordan Papers SC0058
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - General Correspondence, 1872-1931; Series I-A
    - 1897, Jan 26-31, and undated (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - 1897, February 1-5 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - 1897, February 6-12 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - 1897, February 13-20 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - 1897, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - 1897, March 1-9 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - 1897, March 10-19 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - 1897, Mar 20-31, and undated (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - 1897, April 1-5 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - 1897, April 6-10 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - 1897, April 11-15 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - 1897, April 16-20 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - 1897, Apr 21-30, and undated (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - 1897, May 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - 1897, May 11-15 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - 1897, May 16-20 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - 1897, May 21-29, and undated (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - 1897, June 1-5 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - 1897, June 6-15 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - 1897, Jun 17-30, and undated (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - 1897, July (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - 1897, August (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - 1897, September 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - 1897, September 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    - 1897, Sep ember 21-30, and undated (Box 16, Folder 158)
    - 1897, October 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - 1897, October 11-30 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - 1897, November (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - 1897, December 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - 1897, December 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - 1897, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - 1898, January 1-15 (Box 17, Folder 165)
    - 1898, Jan 16-31, and undated (Box 17, Folder 166)
    - 1898, February 1-15 (Box 17, Folder 167)
    - 1898, February 16-28 (Box 17, Folder 168)
    - 1898, March 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 169)
    - 1898, March 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 170)
    - 1898, Mar 21-31, and undated (Box 17, Folder 171)
    - 1898, April 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 172)
    - 1898, April 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    - 1898, Apr 21-30, and undated (Box 17, Folder 174)
    - 1898, May 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - 1898, May 11-31, and undated (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - 1898, June 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 177)
    - 1898, Jun 16-30, and undated (Box 18, Folder 178)
    - 1898, July 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - 1898, Jul 16-31, and undated (Box 18, Folder 180)
    - 1898, August 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - 1898, Aug 16-31, and undated (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - 1898, September 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 183)
    - 1898, Sep ember 16-30, and undated (Box 18, Folder 184)
    - 1898, October 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 185)
    - 1898, October 10-20 (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - 1898, Oct 21-31, and undated (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - 1898, November 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 188)
    - 1898, November 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 189)
    - 1898, Nov 21-30, and undated (Box 19, Folder 190)
    - 1898, December 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 191)
    - 1898, December 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 192)
    - 1898, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 19, Folder 193)
    - 1898, undated (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - 1899, January 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - 1899, January 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - 1899, Jan 21-31, and undated (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - 1899, February 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 198)
    - 1899, February 11-15 (Box 20, Folder 199)
    - 1899, February 16-20 (Box 20, Folder 200)
    - 1899, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 20, Folder 201)
    - 1899, March 1-7 (Box 20, Folder 202)
    - 1899, March 8-15 (Box 20, Folder 203)
    - 1899, March 16-20 (Box 21, Folder 204)
    - 1899, March 21-25 (Box 21, Folder 205)
    - 1899, Mar 26-31, and undated (Box 21, Folder 206)
    - 1899, April 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 207)
    - 1899, April 11-15 (Box 21, Folder 208)
    - 1899, April 16-20 (Box 21, Folder 209)
    - 1899, April 21-25 (Box 21, Folder 210)
    - 1899, Apr 26-30, and undated (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - 1899, May 1-5 (Box 22, Folder 212)
    - 1899, May 6-10 (Box 22, Folder 213)
    - 1899, May 11-15 (Box 22, Folder 214)
    - 1899, May 16-20 (Box 22, Folder 215)
    - 1899, May 21-25 (Box 22, Folder 216)
    - 1899, May 26-31, and undated (Box 22, Folder 217)
    - 1899, June 1-5 (Box 22, Folder 218)
    - 1899, June 6-10 (Box 22, Folder 219)
    - 1899, June 11-15 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - 1899, June 16-20 (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - 1899, June 21-25 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - 1899, Jun 26-30, and undated (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - 1899, July 1-10 (Box 23, Folder 224)
    - 1899, July 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - 1899, Jul 21-31, and undated (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - 1899, August 1-10 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - 1899, August 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - 1899, August 21-31 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - 1899, September 1-10 (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - 1899, September 11-20 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - 1899, Sep ember 21-31, and undated (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - 1899, October 1-15 (Box 24, Folder 233a)
    - 1899, Oct 16-31, and undated (Box 24, Folder 233b)
    - 1899, November 1-15 (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - 1899, Nov 16-30, and undated (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - 1899, December 1-10 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - 1899, December 11-20 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - 1899, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - 1899, undated (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - 1900, January 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 240)
    - 1900, January 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - 1900, January 21-25 (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - 1900, Jan 26-31, and undated (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - 1900, February 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - 1900, February 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - 1900, February 21-28 (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - 1900, March 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 247)
    - 1900, March 11-20 (Box 25, Folder 248)
    - 1900, Mar 21-31, and undated (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - 1900, April 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - 1900, April 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - 1900, April 21-30 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - 1900, May 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - 1900, May 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - 1900, May 21-31, and undated (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - 1900, June 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 256)
    - 1900, June 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 257)
    - 1900, Jun 21-30, and undated (Box 26, Folder 258)
    - 1900, Jul 1-31, and undated (Box 26, Folder 259)
    - 1900, August 1-15 (Box 26, Folder 260)
    - 1900, Aug 16-31, and undated (Box 26, Folder 261)
    - 1900, September 1-15 (Box 27, Folder 262)
    - 1900, September 16-30 (Box 27, Folder 263)
    - 1900, October 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 264)
    - 1900, October 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 265)
    - 1900, Oct 21-31, and undated (Box 27, Folder 266)
    - 1900, November 1-7 (Box 27, Folder 267)
    - 1900, November 8-10 (Box 27, Folder 268)
    - 1900, November 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 269)
    - 1900, Nov 21-30, and undated (Box 27, Folder 270)
    - 1900, December 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 271)
    - 1900, December 11-20 (Box 27, Folder 272)
    - 1900, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - 1901, January 1-10 (Box 27, Folder 274)
    - 1901, January 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - 1901, January 21-31 (Box 28, Folder 276)
    - 1901, February 1-15 (Box 28, Folder 277)
    - 1901, February 16-29 (Box 28, Folder 278)
    - 1901, March 1-10 (Box 28, Folder 279)
    - 1901, March 11-20 (Box 28, Folder 280)
    - 1901, Mar 21-31, and undated (Box 28, Folder 281)
    - 1901, April 1-15 (Box 28, Folder 282)
    - 1901, Apr 16-30, and undated (Box 28, Folder 283)
    - 1901, May 1-15 (Box 28, Folder 284)
    - 1901, May 16-31 (Box 28, Folder 285)
    - 1901, June 1-30 (Box 29, Folder 286)
    - 1901, July 1-20 (Box 29, Folder 287)
    - 1901, July 21-31 (Box 29, Folder 288)
    - 1901, August 1-15 (Box 29, Folder 289)
    - 1901, August 16-31 (Box 29, Folder 290)
    - 1901, September 1-15 (Box 29, Folder 291)
    - 1901, September 16-30 (Box 29, Folder 292)
    - 1901, October 1-15 (Box 29, Folder 293)
    - 1901, Oct 16-31, and undated (Box 29, Folder 294)
    - 1901, November 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 295)
    - 1901, November 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 296)
    - 1901, Nov 21-30, and undated (Box 30, Folder 297)
    - 1901, December 1-10 (Box 30, Folder 298)
    - 1901, December 11-20 (Box 30, Folder 299)
    - 1901, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 30, Folder 300)
    - 1902, January 1-8 (Box 30, Folder 301)
    - 1902, January 9-15 (Box 30, Folder 302)
    - 1902, January 16-22 (Box 30, Folder 303)
    - 1902, Jan 23-31, and undated (Box 30, Folder 304)
    - 1902, February 1-6 (Box 31, Folder 305)
    - 1902, February 7-14 (Box 31, Folder 306)
    - 1902, Feb 15-28, and undated (Box 31, Folder 307)
    - 1902, March 1-10 (Box 31, Folder 308)
    - 1902, March 11-15 (Box 31, Folder 309)
    - 1902, March 16-22 (Box 31, Folder 310)
    - 1902, Mar 23-31, and undated (Box 31, Folder 311)
    - 1902, April 1-5 (Box 32, Folder 312)
    - 1902, April 6-10 (Box 32, Folder 313)
    - 1902, April 11-15 (Box 32, Folder 314)
    - 1902, April 16-22 (Box 32, Folder 315)
    - 1902, Apr 23-30, and undated (Box 32, Folder 316)
    - 1902, May 1-10 (Box 32, Folder 317)
    - 1902, May 11-20 (Box 32, Folder 318)
    - 1902, May 21-26 (Box 32, Folder 319)
    - 1902, May 27-31, and undated (Box 32, Folder 320)
    - 1902, June (Box 33, Folder 321)
    - 1902, July (Box 33, Folder 322)
    - 1902, August (Box 33, Folder 323)
    - 1902, September 1-7 (Box 33, Folder 324)
    - 1902, September 8-15 (Box 33, Folder 325)
    - 1902, September 16-20 (Box 33, Folder 326)
    - 1902, Sep ember 21-31, and undated (Box 33, Folder 327)
    - 1902, October 1-5 (Box 33, Folder 328)
    - 1902, October 6-10 (Box 33, Folder 329)
    - 1902, October 11-15 (Box 34, Folder 330)
    - 1902, October 16-21 (Box 34, Folder 331)
    - 1902, October 22-31 (Box 34, Folder 332)
    - 1902, November 1-5 (Box 34, Folder 333)
    - 1902, November 6-10 (Box 34, Folder 334)
    - 1902, November 11-17 (Box 34, Folder 335)
    - 1902, November 18-23 (Box 34, Folder 336)
    - 1902, Nov 24-31, and undated (Box 34, Folder 337)
    - 1902, December 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 338)
    - 1902, December 6-11 (Box 35, Folder 339)
    - 1902, December 12-17 (Box 35, Folder 340)
    - 1902, December 18-20 (Box 35, Folder 341)
    - 1902, December 21-26 (Box 35, Folder 342)
    - 1902, Dec 27-31, and undated (Box 35, Folder 343)
    - 1902, undated (Box 35, Folder 344)
    - 1903, January 1-15 (Box 35, Folder 345)
    - 1903, January 16-25 (Box 35, Folder 346)
    - 1903, Jan 26-31, and undated (Box 35, Folder 347)
    - 1903, February 1-10 (Box 36, Folder 348)
    - 1903, February 11-20 (Box 36, Folder 349)
    - 1903, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 36, Folder 350)
    - 1903, March 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 351)
    - 1903, March 5-15 (Box 36, Folder 352)
    - 1903, March 16-25 (Box 36, Folder 353)
    - 1903, Mar 26-31, and undated (Box 36, Folder 354)
    - 1903, April 1-10 (Box 36, Folder 355)
    - 1903, April 11-20 (Box 36, Folder 356)
    - 1903, April 21-30 (Box 36, Folder 357)
    - 1903, May 1-10 (Box 37, Folder 358)
    - 1903, May 11-20 (Box 37, Folder 359)
    - 1903, May 21-31, and undated (Box 37, Folder 360)
    - 1903, June 1-10 (Box 37, Folder 361)
    - 1903, June 11-20 (Box 37, Folder 362)
    - 1903, Jun 21-30, and undated (Box 37, Folder 363)
    - 1903, July 1-15 (Box 37, Folder 364)
    - 1903, Jul 16-31, and undated (Box 37, Folder 365)
    - 1903, Aug 1-30, and undated (Box 37, Folder 366)
    - 1903, September 1-15 (Box 37, Folder 367)
    - 1903, Sep ember 16-30, and undated (Box 37, Folder 368)
    - 1903, October 1-10 (Box 38, Folder 369)
    - 1903, October 11-20 (Box 38, Folder 370)
    - 1903, October 21-31 (Box 38, Folder 371)
    - 1903, November 1-10 (Box 38, Folder 372)
    - 1903, November 11-20 (Box 38, Folder 373)
    - 1903, Nov 21-30, and undated (Box 38, Folder 374)
    - 1903, December 1-10 (Box 38, Folder 375)
    - 1903, December 11-20 (Box 38, Folder 376)
    - 1903, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 38, Folder 377)
    - 1903, undated (Box 38, Folder 378)
    - 1904, January 1-10 (Box 39, Folder 379)
    - 1904, January 11-20 (Box 39, Folder 380)
    - 1904, Jan 21-31, and undated (Box 39, Folder 381)
    - 1904, February 1-10 (Box 39, Folder 382)
    - 1904, February 11-20 (Box 39, Folder 383)
    - 1904, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 39, Folder 384)
    - 1904, March 1-6 (Box 39, Folder 385)
    - 1904, March 7-15 (Box 39, Folder 386)
    - 1904, March 16-20 (Box 39, Folder 387)
    - 1904, Mar 21-31, and undated (Box 39, Folder 388)
    - 1904, April 1-7 (Box 40, Folder 389)
    - 1904, April 8-15 (Box 40, Folder 390)
    - 1904, April 16-22 (Box 40, Folder 391)
    - 1904, April 23-30 (Box 40, Folder 392)
    - 1904, April, undated (Box 40, Folder 393)
    - 1904, May 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 394)
    - 1904, May 6-15 (Box 40, Folder 395)
    - 1904, May 16-20 (Box 40, Folder 396)
    - 1904, May 21-31 (Box 40, Folder 397)
    - 1904, May, undated (Box 40, Folder 398)
    - 1904, June 1-10 (Box 40, Folder 399)
    - 1904, June 11-20 (Box 40, Folder 400)
    - 1904, June 21-30 (Box 40, Folder 401)
    - 1904, June, undated (Box 40, Folder 402)
    - 1904, July 1-10 (Box 41, Folder 403)
    - 1904, July 11-20 (Box 41, Folder 404)
    - 1904, July 21-31 (Box 41, Folder 405)
    - 1904, July, undated (Box 41, Folder 406)
    - 1904, August 1-5 (Box 41, Folder 407)
    - 1904, August 6-12 (Box 41, Folder 408)
    - 1904, August 13-20 (Box 41, Folder 409)
    - 1904, August 21-31 (Box 41, Folder 410)
    - 1904, September 1-7 (Box 41, Folder 411)
    - 1904, September 8-15 (Box 41, Folder 412)
    - 1904, September 16-22 (Box 41, Folder 413)
    - 1904, Sep ember 23-30, and undated (Box 41, Folder 414)
    - 1904, October 1-5 (Box 42, Folder 415)
    - 1904, October 6-10 (Box 42, Folder 416)
    - 1904, October 11-17 (Box 42, Folder 417)
    - 1904, October 18-21 (Box 42, Folder 418)
    - 1904, Oct 22-31, and undated (Box 42, Folder 419)
    - 1904, November 1-5 (Box 42, Folder 420)
    - 1904, November 6-10 (Box 42, Folder 421)
    - 1904, November 11-17 (Box 42, Folder 422)
    - 1904, November 18-25 (Box 42, Folder 423)
    - 1904, Nov 26-30, and undated (Box 42, Folder 424)
    - 1904, December 1-5 (Box 42, Folder 425)
    - 1904, December 6-10 (Box 42, Folder 426)
    - 1904, December 11-15 (Box 42, Folder 427)
    - 1904, December 16-22 (Box 42, Folder 428)
    - 1904, December 23-31 (Box 42, Folder 429)
    - 1904, December, undated (Box 42, Folder 430)
    - 1905, January 1-6 (Box 43, Folder 431)
    - 1905, January 7-13 (Box 43, Folder 432)
    - 1905, January 14-20 (Box 43, Folder 433)
    - 1905, January 21-25 (Box 43, Folder 434)
    - 1905, Jan 26-31, and undated (Box 43, Folder 435)
    - 1905, February 1-5 (Box 43, Folder 436)
    - 1905, February 6-13 (Box 43, Folder 437)
    - 1905, February 14-18 (Box 43, Folder 438)
    - 1905, Feb 20-28, and undated (Box 43, Folder 439)
    - 1905, March 1-5 (Box 44, Folder 440)
    - 1905, March 6-10 (Box 44, Folder 441)
    - 1905, March 11-16 (Box 44, Folder 442)
    - 1905, March 17-22 (Box 44, Folder 443)
    - 1905, March 23-27 (Box 44, Folder 444)
    - 1905, Mar 28-31, and undated (Box 44, Folder 445)
    - 1905, April 1-10 (Box 44, Folder 446)
    - 1905, April 11-15 (Box 44, Folder 447)
    - 1905, April 16-20 (Box 44, Folder 448)
    - 1905, April 21-26 (Box 44, Folder 449)
    - 1905, Apr 27-30, and undated (Box 44, Folder 450)
    - 1905, May 1-5 (Box 45, Folder 451)
    - 1905, May 6-10 (Box 45, Folder 452)
    - 1905, May 11-16 (Box 45, Folder 453)
    - 1905, May 17-25 (Box 45, Folder 454)
    - 1905, May 26-31, and undated (Box 45, Folder 455)
    - 1905, June 1-10 (Box 45, Folder 456)
    - 1905, June 11-30 (Box 45, Folder 457)
    - 1905, July 1-15 (Box 45, Folder 458)
    - 1905, Jul 17-31, and undated (Box 45, Folder 459)
    - 1905, August 1-15 (Box 45, Folder 460)
    - 1905, Aug 15-31, and undated (Box 45, Folder 461)
    - 1905, September 1-10 (Box 46, Folder 462)
    - 1905, September 11-19 (Box 46, Folder 463)
    - 1905, Sep ember 20-30, and undated (Box 46, Folder 464)
    - 1905, October 1-10 (Box 46, Folder 465)
    - 1905, October 11-20 (Box 46, Folder 466)
    - 1905, Oct 21-31, and undated (Box 46, Folder 467)
    - 1905, November 1-7 (Box 47, Folder 468)
    - 1905, November 8-15 (Box 47, Folder 469)
    - 1905, Nov 16-30, and undated (Box 47, Folder 470)
    - 1905, December 1-5 (Box 47, Folder 471)
    - 1905, December 6-10 (Box 47, Folder 472)
    - 1905, December 11-15 (Box 47, Folder 473)
    - 1905, December 16-20 (Box 47, Folder 474)
    - 1905, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 47, Folder 475)
    - 1905, undated (Box 47, Folder 476)
    - 1906, January 1-10 (Box 48, Folder 477)
    - 1906, January 11-20 (Box 48, Folder 478)
    - 1906, Jan 21-31, and undated (Box 48, Folder 479)
    - 1906, February 1-10 (Box 48, Folder 480)
    - 1906, February 11-20 (Box 48, Folder 481)
    - 1906, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 48, Folder 482)
    - 1906, March 1-5 (Box 48, Folder 483)
    - 1906, March 6-10 (Box 48, Folder 484)
    - 1906, March 11-15 (Box 48, Folder 485)
    - 1906, March 16-20 (Box 48, Folder 486)
    - 1906, Mar 21-31, and undated (Box 48, Folder 487)
    - 1906, April 1-10 (Box 49, Folder 488)
    - 1906, April 11-20 (Box 49, Folder 489)
    - 1906, Apr 21-30, and undated (Box 49, Folder 490)
    - earthquake letters, 1906, April 18-22 (Box 49, Folder 491)
    - earthquake letters, 1906, April 23-June 1 (Box 49, Folder 492)
    - 1906, May 1-10 (Box 49, Folder 493)
    - 1906, May 11-20 (Box 49, Folder 494)
    - 1906, May 21-31, and undated (Box 49, Folder 495)
    - 1906, June 1-10 (Box 50, Folder 496)
    - 1906, June 11-20 (Box 50, Folder 497)
    - 1906, Jun 21-30, and undated (Box 50, Folder 498)
    - 1906, July 1-10 (Box 50, Folder 499)
    - 1906, July 11-20 (Box 50, Folder 500)
    - 1906, Jul 21-31, and undated (Box 50, Folder 501)
    - 1906, August 1-10 (Box 50, Folder 502)
    - 1906, August 11-20 (Box 50, Folder 503)
    - 1906, Aug 21-31, and undated (Box 50, Folder 504)
    - 1906, September 1-10 (Box 51, Folder 505)
    - 1906, September 11-20 (Box 51, Folder 506)
    - 1906, Sep ember 21-30, and undated (Box 51, Folder 507)
    - 1906, October 1-10 (Box 51, Folder 508)
    - 1906, October 11-20 (Box 51, Folder 509)
    - 1906, Oct 21-31, and undated (Box 51, Folder 510)
    - 1906, November 1-10 (Box 52, Folder 511)
    - 1906, November 11-20 (Box 52, Folder 512)
    - 1906, Nov 21-30, and undated (Box 52, Folder 513)
    - 1906, December 1-10 (Box 52, Folder 514)
    - 1906, December 11-20 (Box 52, Folder 515)
    - 1906, Dec 21-31, and undated (Box 52, Folder 516)
    - 1907, January 1-10 (Box 53, Folder 517)
    - 1907, January 11-15 (Box 53, Folder 518)
    - 1907, January 16-20 (Box 53, Folder 519)
    - 1907, January 21-25 (Box 53, Folder 520)
    - 1907, Jan 26-31, and undated (Box 53, Folder 521)
    - 1907, February 1-7 (Box 53, Folder 522)
    - 1907, February 8-15 (Box 53, Folder 523)
    - 1907, February 16-21 (Box 53, Folder 524)
    - 1907, Feb 22-28, and undated (Box 53, Folder 525)
    - 1907, March 1-7 (Box 54, Folder 526)
    - 1907, March 8-18 (Box 54, Folder 527)
    - 1907, March 19-25 (Box 54, Folder 528)
    - 1907, March 26-31 (Box 54, Folder 529)
    - 1907, April 1-15 (Box 54, Folder 530)
    - 1907, Apr 16-30, and undated (Box 54, Folder 531)
    - 1907, May 1-31, and undated (Box 54, Folder 532)
    - 1907, June 1-10 (Box 55, Folder 533)
    - 1907, June 11-20 (Box 55, Folder 534)
    - 1907, Jun 21-30, and undated (Box 55, Folder 535)
    - 1907, July 1-13 (Box 55, Folder 536)
    - 1907, July 14-31 (Box 55, Folder 537)
    - 1907, August 1-8 (Box 55, Folder 538)
    - 1907, August 9-20 (Box 55, Folder 539)
    - 1907, Aug 21-31, and undated (Box 55, Folder 540)
    - 1907, September 1-13 (Box 56, Folder 541)
    - 1907, September 14-21 (Box 56, Folder 542)
    - 1907, Sep ember 22-30, and undated (Box 56, Folder 543)
    - 1907, October 1-9 (Box 56, Folder 544)
    - 1907, October 10-19 (Box 56, Folder 545)
    - 1907, Oct 20-31, and undated (Box 56, Folder 546)
    - 1907, November 1-8 (Box 56, Folder 547)
    - 1907, November 9-20 (Box 57, Folder 548)
    - 1907, November 21-30 (Box 57, Folder 549)
    - 1907, December 1-10 (Box 57, Folder 550)
    - 1907, December 11-22 (Box 57, Folder 551)
    - 1907, December 23-28 (Box 57, Folder 552)
    - 1907, Dec 29-31, and undated (Box 57, Folder 553)
    - 1908, January 1-8 (Box 58, Folder 554)
    - 1908, January 9-15 (Box 58, Folder 555)
    - 1908, January 16-21 (Box 58, Folder 556)
    - 1908, January 22-27 (Box 58, Folder 557)
    - 1908, January 28-31 (Box 58, Folder 558)
    - 1908, February 1-10 (Box 58, Folder 559)
    - 1908, February 11-17 (Box 58, Folder 560)
    - 1908, February 18-24 (Box 58, Folder 561)
    - 1908, Feb 25-29, and undated (Box 58, Folder 562)
    - 1908, March 1-6 (Box 58, Folder 563)
    - 1908, March 7-17 (Box 58, Folder 564)
    - 1908, March 18-24 (Box 58, Folder 565)
    - 1908, March 25-31 (Box 58, Folder 566)
    - 1908, April 1-11 (Box 59, Folder 567)
    - 1908, April 12-21 (Box 59, Folder 568)
    - 1908, April 22-31 (Box 59, Folder 569)
    - 1908, May 1-11 (Box 59, Folder 570)
    - 1908, May 12-16 (Box 59, Folder 571)
    - 1908, May 17-22 (Box 59, Folder 572)
    - 1908, May 23-31 (Box 59, Folder 573)
    - 1908, June 1-9 (Box 59, Folder 574)
    - 1908, June 10-16 (Box 59, Folder 575)
    - 1908, June 17-24 (Box 59, Folder 576)
    - 1908, June 25-30 (Box 59, Folder 577)
    - 1908, July 1-14 (Box 60, Folder 578)
    - 1908, July 15-31 (Box 60, Folder 579)
    - 1908, August 1-17 (Box 60, Folder 580)
    - 1908, August 18-24 (Box 60, Folder 581)
    - 1908, August 25-31 (Box 60, Folder 582)
    - 1908, September 1-11 (Box 60, Folder 583)
    - 1908, September 12-21 (Box 60, Folder 584)
    - 1908, September 22-30 (Box 60, Folder 585)
    - 1908, October 1-11 (Box 60, Folder 586)
    - 1908, October 12-19 (Box 60, Folder 587)
    - 1908, October 20-27 (Box 60, Folder 588)
    - 1908, October 28-31 (Box 60, Folder 589)
    - 1908, November 1-9 (Box 61, Folder 590)
    - 1908, November 10-22 (Box 61, Folder 591)
    - 1908, Nov 23-30, and undated (Box 61, Folder 592)
    - 1908, December 1-9 (Box 61, Folder 593)
    - 1908, December 10-18 (Box 61, Folder 594)
    - 1908, Dec 19-31, and undated (Box 61, Folder 595)
    - 1909, January 1-8 (Box 61, Folder 596)
    - 1909, January 9-18 (Box 61, Folder 597)
    - 1909, January 19-26 (Box 62, Folder 598)
    - 1909, Jan 27-31, and undated (Box 61, Folder 599)
    - 1909, February 1-10 (Box 61, Folder 600)
    - 1909, February 11-18 (Box 61, Folder 601)
    - 1909, Feb 19-28, and undated (Box 61, Folder 602)
    - 1909, March 1-9 (Box 61, Folder 603)
    - 1909, March 10-19 (Box 61, Folder 604)
    - 1909, Mar 20-31, and undated (Box 61, Folder 605)
    - 1909, April 1-10 (Box 63, Folder 606)
    - 1909, April 11-22 (Box 61, Folder 607)
    - 1909, Apr 23-30, and undated (Box 61, Folder 608)
    - 1909, May 1-10 (Box 61, Folder 609)
    - 1909, May 11-20 (Box 61, Folder 610)
    - 1909, May 21-31, and undated (Box 61, Folder 611)
    - 1909, June 1-14 (Box 61, Folder 612)
    - 1909, Jun 15-30, and undated (Box 64, Folder 613)
    - 1909, July 1-16 (Box 64, Folder 614)
    - 1909, Jul 17-31, and undated (Box 64, Folder 615)
    - 1909, August (Box 64, Folder 616)
    - 1909, September 1-10 (Box 64, Folder 617)
    - 1909, September 11-23 (Box 64, Folder 618)
    - 1909, Sep ember 24-30, and undated (Box 64, Folder 619)
    - 1909, October 1-13 (Box 64, Folder 620)
    - 1909, October 14-27 (Box 65, Folder 621)
    - 1909, Oct 28-31, and undated (Box 65, Folder 622)
    - 1909, November 1-10 (Box 65, Folder 623)
    - 1909, November 11-23 (Box 65, Folder 624)
    - 1909, Nov 24-30, and undated (Box 65, Folder 625)
    - 1909, December 1-13 (Box 65, Folder 626)
    - 1909, December 14-19 (Box 65, Folder 627)